Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum D
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Conferences and Programs, 1981-1992; Series VI
  - Asian Women's Educational Concerns, 1981-1985 (Box 23, Folder 313)
  - Commision on Women and Work (AWI), 1978-1988 (Box 23, Folder 314)
  - Women's Program; Meeting for resource manual, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 315)
  - Asian Consultation of Women't Concerns, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 316)
  - Women's Newsletter and Address book, 1985 Jun-1990 Jan (Box 23, Folder 317)
- Financial Records, 1979-1990; Series VII
  - Budgets and statements
    - Proposed Budget to UB Trustees, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 317a)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 318)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 319)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 320)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 321)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 322)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 323)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 324)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 325)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 326)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 327)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 328)
  - Estates
    - Sie, Ping Teh (Box 25, Folder 329)
    - Stanwick, Sophie E. (Box 25, Folder 330)